(Raj:)That is so
generous of you.
(Raj:)I'd like to switch sides.
(Howard:)Look, uh...
(Howard:)I don't even think
you can take this wall down
(Howard:)'cause it's load-bearing.
(Raj:)Well, it's easy to find out.
(Raj:)Just go into the crawlspace
under the house and check.
(Howard:)When is your visa up?
(Sheldon:)Not only is it signed to me
(Sheldon:)but this is where he wiped
his mouth.
(Sheldon:)So we are currently in the
presence of Leonard Nimoy's DNA.
(Wil:)Um, doesn't Adam count
as Leonard Nimoy's DNA?
No offense, but this is
pure 100% Nimoy.
(Sheldon:)Because of your mother,
you're only 50%.
(Sheldon:)Which isn't bad,
(Sheldon:)but anything that you wipe
your mouth on gets thrown away.
(Penny:)Okay, enough
about the napkin.
(Penny:)What else you
hiding in there?
(Sheldon:)Wouldn't you like
to know?
(Penny:)I would.
All right then.
(Sheldon:)See? Just my valuables.
(Sheldon:)My passport, uh, my will...
You have a will?
(Sheldon:)Yeah... my 1/18 scale
Wil Wheaton action figure.